jsexnetwork.com 2006-06-15

# JSN

**Privacy Policy**

Last Updated: May 30, 2004

At JSexNetwork.com we understand and believe that your personal information is of high importance. You should be able to choose what information you want to share and what is not. The policies below are applicable to JSexNetwork.com and its subdomains on the World Wide Web. Please read the following carefully: 

**General Information on Collection and Use**  
Anyone over the age of 18 years old can visit any of the JSexNetwork.com web sites without disclosing who they are or revealing any personal information about themselves. At JSexNetwork.com, we only track the Internet addresses of the individuals who visit our site to analyze trends, and traffic and only track user's movement within the site to gather broad demographic information. The data we gather is not linked in any way to individual personally identifiable information. The information we collect is mainly for our own marketing strategy in understanding the main demographics of our most popular region of visitors and not individual visitors. All information is confidential and will never be sold or disclosed to a third party.

**Encrypted Credit Card Purchases**  
When you use a credit card to purchase a JSexNetwork.com subscription, the credit card number is encrypted as it passes over the Internet. Your credit card number is not kept or recorded on our computers - it is simply passed through to the credit card company to purchase the subscription. In addition, we are sensitive to the fact that some users are uncomfortable submitting their credit card number over the Internet, no matter how secure the environment. 

**Notification of Changes**  
At JSexNetwork.com Corporation when we make any changes to our privacy policy, we will post the changes on our site so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, how we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use our customer's personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we would notify you via email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. 

**Cookies**  
JSexNetwork.com does not use cookies. A cookie is a small text file, stored in memory on your computer that can be read by our system when you return to our site. The cookies are encrypted and are used to keep track of you as you move through our site. Cookies provide you the ability to re-enter a page without retyping your password and the ability to return directly to your last accessed page in any form for a specific, predetermined period of time. While cookies allow you ease of use by entering your Password less frequently, there are no functional differences if the site is accessed and used with the cookies disabled. 

**Disclosure**  
JSexNetwork.com will not sell, rent, trade, or disclose individual Customer information to any third parties or outside companies who will use the information to contact you or who will share the information with others without your permission. It may be necessary to disclose information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal actions against someone who may be violating JSexNetwork.com policies or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the rights or property of JSexNetwork.com. JSexNetwork.com may disclose or allow access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our services. 

**Use of Information**  
At JSexNetwork.com, we only keep a record of the subscribing members e-mail addresses and adresses for only 30 days after the expiration of their subscription membership. All information is discarded and permanently purged after 30 days after expiration.

**Member E-mails**  
JSexNetwork.com has a strict regulation towards disclosing client email content to others unless required by a lawful agency or through by interference to our products and services due to the client. Our strict privacy statement is enforced by all our supporting staff.
